# **Gares Luis**

# Blockchain/Full-Stack Developer

As a passionate and skilled Blockchain/Full-Stack Developer with 6 years of relevant experience, my goal and objective are to contribute my blockchain technology and skills to your company.

- Proficient at performing well as working in a group or independently in a fast-paced setting.
- Deep understanding and hands-on experience in Decentralized Blockchain applications: Smart contracts, DApps, Defi, Gamefi, Dex using Ethereum and Solana.

#### **CONTACT**

+852 81746669

Crispalp13@gmail.com

9K Recreation Lane, Singapore

hackerrank.com/GaresLuis

in LinkedIn.com/in/GaresLuis

GitHub.com/in/Nabi1020-dev

#### **EDUCATION**

### **Bachelor's Degree**

Computer Science Nanyang Technological University, 2013-2017

# **SKILLS**

## Full-Stack Developer.

- C/C++, JScript/TScript
- Python/ Django/ Flask
- Node.js/ Express
- React/ Redux/ Hook/ Next.js
- Vue/ VueX/ Nuxt
- MongoDB/PostgresSQL

#### Blockchain Developer.

- Solidity/ Rust/ Scrypto
- ERC20/ ERC721/ ERC1155/ FNFT
- Truffle/ Hardhat/ Web3/ Alchemy
- Defi/ Dapps/ Gamefi/ Dex
- Bitcoin/ Ethereum/ Hedera/
  Solana/ Polygon/ Hyper-Ledger

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Blockchain / Full-Stack Developer**

RockX, Singapore | Jul.2020 - Apr.2022

Researched Web3, Defi, Gamefi, Dex and develop internal applications as well as external products, and worked on other blockchain technology

- On-Chain data access through APIs
- Collaborations with synergistic partners & innovative blockchains that drive the future of Web 3.0
- Other Work Experience
- -Developed Foundation.app NFT marketplace (Next.js, Graph QL, Truffle, Ethereum)
- -Developed MintySwap (Next.js, Hardhat, Alchemy, Polygon)

**Technical Environment**: React-Hook, Material-UI, Next.js, Remix.js, Graph QL, Solidity, Web3, Ethereum, Polygon, Hedera, Truffle

### **Blockchain Developer**

Vasilkoff CY.LTD| Jan.2019 - Jul.2020

- Developed ERC20 token called XFB that has the deflationary mechanism according to time-weighted average price oracle on Uni-swap v2
- Created a new token called Mooni, built a smart contract for the Mooni token, and deployed it to the BSC chain

Technical Environment: React-Hook, Material-UI, Solidity, Web3.js, ERC20, Truffle

### Python/ Node Full-Stack Developer

VI Dimension, Singapore | Jan.2017 -Dec.2018

- ✓ Constructed 100% serverless APIs backend using Lambda functions coded by Claudia.js, which is a dedicated serverless API node.js based framework
- ☑ Built a static web app with React.js for the front-end which would be hosted on the AWS S3 bucket.
- Developed data quality portal using Python scripting, increasing data quality by 30% and maintained large databases and configured services to reduce software maintenance expenses, decreasing the costs by 15% within just a year.

Technical Environment: Python, Node, AWS Lambda, MERN, API, Machine Learning